(Sheldon:)because my university
(Sheldon:)was making me do
string theory,
(Sheldon:)and my favorite comic
book store burned down,
and when my roommate
got engaged,
(Sheldon:)my girlfriend wanted
to move in with me,
(Sheldon:)which was no doubt
a ploy just to see my...
(Sheldon:)Well, excuse my language,
but my bathing suit parts.
(Sheldon:)Uh, sir, may I
use your phone?
(Man:)I don't think so.
Yeah, well,
(Sheldon:)I understand that
I'm half naked,
(Sheldon:)but there is
a reasonable explanation.
(Sheldon:)While I slept
in my sleeper car,
(Sheldon:)all my possessions were stolen.
(Sheldon:)Now,
(Sheldon:)typically,
I wear pajamas,
(Sheldon:)but I recently adopted
a hobo lifestyle
and pajamas are the
sleep-pants of the Man.
(Sheldon:)I'll have you know,
Mahatma Gandhi wore no pants
and a nation rallied behind him!
(Sheldon:)My good man...
(Sheldon:)Now, before you walk away...
(Sheldon:)I know that I may
appear deranged,
(Sheldon:)but I am, in fact,
a world-renowned physicist.
(Sheldon:)Ask me the difference
between a boson and a fermion.
Go ahead, ask!
(Sheldon:)Bosons have integer spin,
fermions have half-integer spin!
My legs are getting cold!
(Sheldon:)Why won't anybody help me?